Kenneth Hazen Aynesworth papers, Inclusive: 1826-1965, undated, Bulk: 1930-1943
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Family, 1826-1965, undated; 1
  - General, 1830-1965, undated; 3; This subseries contains two document boxes.
    - Family: General: Forbes Family, 1869-1897 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Family: General: Harry Gamble, 1905-1950 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Family: General: Hickman Family, 1870-1910 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Family: General: Charles C. Hickman, 1830-1940 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Family: General: J.C. Hickman, 1874-1897 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Family: General: N.F. Hickman, 1865-1891 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Family: General: Sam Hickman, 1867 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Family: General: Susan A. Hickman, 1880-1895 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Family: General: Susan A. McClain, 1873-1878 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Correspondence, 1898-1944, undated; 2
  This series contains sent correspondence, received correspondence, cards, and classifed correspondence involving Dr. Kenneth Aynesworth. Topics of these letters include politics, history, medicine, business, and education. The materials are in good condition.
  - Received, 1899-1944, undated; 1; This subseries contains fourteen document boxes.
    The following subseries contains correspondence written to Kenneth Aynesworth from friends and co-workers. The materials are organized chronologically and are in average to good condition.
    The materials are organized chronologically.
    - General, 1899-1902 June (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - General, 1902 July-August (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - General, 1903-1911 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - General, 1912 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - General, 1922-1926 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - General, 1927-1929 June 5 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - General, 1929 June 29 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - General, 1929 August-November 6 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - General, 1929 November 7-23 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - General, 1929 December (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - General, 1930 January 2-18 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - General, 1930 January 24- February 14 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - General, 1930 February 15- March 12 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - General, 1930 March 14- May 7 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - General, 1930 May 9-27 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - General, 1930 June 3-5 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - General, 1930 June 6-25 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - General, 1930 June 26-July 16 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - General, 1930 July 19-26 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - General, 1930 July 29-August (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - General, 1930 September 1-20 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - General, 1930 September 24- October 4 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - General, 1930 October 6-21 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - General, 1930 October 23-29 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - General, 1930 November (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - General, 1930 December (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - General, 1931 January 1-20 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - General, 1931 January 21-26 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - General, 1931 January 27- February 3 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - General, 1931 February 4-21 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - General, 1931 February 22- March 10 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - General, 1931 March 11-23 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - General, 1931 March 23- April 1 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - General, 1931 April 4- May 5 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - General, 1931 May 6-31 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - General, 1931 June (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - General, 1931 July- August 4 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - General, 1931 August 5-31 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - General, 1931 September 1-4 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - General, 1931 September 4-9 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - General, 1931 September 10-15 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - General, 1931 September 16- October 23 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - General, 1931 October 25- November 17 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - General, 1931 November 18- December 15 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - General, 1931 December 15-28 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - General, 1932 January- February (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - General, 1932 March 2-11 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - General, 1932 March 12-22 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - General, 1932 April 1-6 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - General, 1932 April 8-29 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - General, 1932 May 2-26 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - General, 1932 May 30-June (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - General, 1932 July (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - General, 1932 August (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - General, 1932 September 1-28 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - General, 1932 September 30- October 14 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - General, 1932 October 14-18 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - General, 1932 October 20-30 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - General, 1932 November 1-7 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - General, 1932 November 8-23 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - General, 1932 November 25-30 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - General, 1932 December (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - General, 1933 January 1-9 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - General, 1933 January 9-14 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - General, 1933 January 17-25 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - General, 1933 January 27- February 3 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - General, 1933 February 4-11 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - General, 1933 February 13-16 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - General, 1933 February 17-27 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - General, 1933 February 27- March 11 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - General, 1933 March 12-22 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - General, 1933 March 24-28 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - General, 1933 March 28-April 3 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - General, 1933 April 4-12 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - General, 1933 April 13-26 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - General, 1933 May 1-10 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - General, 1933 May 12-22 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - General, 1933 May 23-31 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - General, 1933 June 1-12 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - General, 1933 June 14-27 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - General, 1933 July (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - General, 1933 August (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - General, 1933 September 1-13 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - General, 1933 September 14- October 6 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - General, 1933 October 7-26 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - General, 1933 October 26- November 2 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - General, 1933 November 6-18 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - General, 1933 November 21- December 11 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - General, 1933 December 12-28 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - General, 1934 January 3-8 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - General, 1934 January 8-22 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1934 January 25- February 3 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1934 February 5-13 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1934 February 13-21 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1934 February 22-28 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1934 March 1-8 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1934 March 9-20 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1934 March 21-29 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1934 April 3-17 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1934 April 19-27 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1934 April 27- May 10 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1934 May 10-18 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1934 May 22- June 9 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1934 June 12-19 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1934 June 22- July 6 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1934 July 9- August 17 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1934 August 20- September 6 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1934 September 15-23 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1934 September 24- October 25 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1934 October 29- November 15 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1934 November 16-30 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1934 December 3-18 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1934 December 20-29 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1935 January 2-25 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1935 January 30- February 9 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1935 February 13- March 19 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1935 March 23- April 6 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1935 April 8-22 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1935 April 26-May 16 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1935 May 22 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1935 May 25- June 11 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1935 June 17- July 9 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1935 July 10-23 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1935 July 29- September 3 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1935 September 5- October 2 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1935 October 6-22 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1935 October 24- November 4 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1935 November 5-13 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1935 November 14-27 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1935 November 28- December 7 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1935 December 9-16 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1935 December 17-31 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1936 January 1-17 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1936 January 18- February 5 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1936 February 6-25 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1936 March 2-16 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1936 March 20- April 6 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1936 April 6-30 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1936 May 4-12 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1936 May 14- June 5 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1936 June 8-17 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1936 June 18-30 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1936 July 1-23 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1936 July 23- August 3 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1936 August 3- September 8 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1936 September 9- October 7 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1936 October 14-27 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1936 November 2-18 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1936 November 25- December 5 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1936 December 9-31 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 January 1-23 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 January 25- February 3 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 February 8-22 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 February 23- March 16 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 March 16-31 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 April 1-20 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 April 22- May 5 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 May 10-20 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 May 21-29 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 June 1-9 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 June 10-17 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 June 18-28 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 June 28- July 8 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 July 9-31 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 August 2-21 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 August 23- September 15 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 September 16-30 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 October 2-19 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 October 20-25 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 October 29- November 3 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 November 4-23 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 November 24- December 3 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 December 3-7 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 December 8-18 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 December 18-27 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1937 December 27-30 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1938 January 1-11 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1938 January 11-21 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1938 January 22-26 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1938 January 26- February 5 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1938 February 8-21 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1938 February 23- March 8 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1938 March 9-23 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1938 March 25- April 14 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1938 April 26-May 11 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1938 May 12-31 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1938 June 1-7 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1938 June 10-11 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1938 June 13-28 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1938 June 29- July 13 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1938 July 14- August 1 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1938 August 3-20 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1938 August 22- September 27 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1938 September 29- October 7 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1938 October 10-25 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1938 October 26- November 11 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1938 November 12-23 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1938 November 23-29 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1938 November 30- December 6 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1938 December 7-14 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1938 December 15-31 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1939 January 4-17 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1939 January 18-25 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1939 January 26- February 6 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1939 February 8-25 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1939 March 2-16 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1939 March 20- April 7 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1939 April 12-29 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1939 May 1-9 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1939 May 10-19 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1939 May 19- June 9 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1939 June 10-23 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1939 June 23-27 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1939 June 27- July 15 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1939 July 22- August 1 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1939 August 8-18 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1939 August 29- September 12 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1939 September 13-28 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1939 October 1-12 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1939 October 13-29 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1939 October 30- November 17 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1939 November 20- December 4 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1939 December 5-21 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1939 December 27-31 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1940 January 2-19 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1940 January 20- February 5 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1940 February 6-15 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1940 February 17- March 7 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1940 March 8-27 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1940 March 28-April 12 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1940 April 12-24 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1940 April 26-May 19 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1940 May 20- June 1 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1940 June 6-21 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1940 June 23-29 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1940 July 1-11 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1940 July 14- August 3 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1940 August 4-13 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1940 August 13-23 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1940 August 27- September 7 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1940 September 10-20 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1940 September 26- October 8 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1940 October 9-21 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1940 October 22- November 6 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1940 November 6-12 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1940 November 12-29 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1940 November 30- December 7 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1940 December 10-11 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1940 December 12-28 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1941 January 2-10 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1941 January 13-25 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1941 January 28- April 13 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1941 April 21- May 8 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1941 May 8- June 9 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1941 June 11-17 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1941 June 17- July 3 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1941 July 4-10 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1941 July 12-31 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1941 August 2-22 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1941 August 23- September 6 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1941 September 8-19 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1941 September 23- October 2 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1941 October 3-17 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1941 October 20- November 3 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1941 November 3-12 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1941 November 13-22 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1941 November 23- December 7 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1941 December 8-14 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1941 December 15-29 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1941 December 29-31 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 January 2-10 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 January 12-30 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 January 30- February 12 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 February 13-28 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 March 2-16 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 March 18-31 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 April 1-2 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 April 3-16 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 April 17-22 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 April 24-30 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 April 30- May 12 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 May 14-31 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 June 2-17 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 June 18-27 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 June 30- July 13 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 July 13-28 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 July 28- August 24 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 August 26- September 3 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 September 5- October 1 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 October 2-14 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 October 14-24 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 October 24- November 9 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 November 10-30 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 November 30- December 1 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 December 4-17 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1942 December 19-31 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1943 January 4-15 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1943 January 15-23 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1943 January 26- February 8 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1943 February 10-23 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1943 February 23- March 9 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1943 March 11- April 8 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1943 April 13- May 5 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1943 May 12- June 2 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1943 June 2-23 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1943 June 23-30 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1943 July 2-12 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1943 July 15-27 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Received: General, 1943 August 2-22 (Box 16, Folder 10)